Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting?
Either way I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high
Hail a brand new dawn
Blaze across the sky Time to journey on On
your mark Come above a
thing We're on Earth,
a legendary
If you can show your breath
Then we'll make some waves
We run our daunted Ain't no
beginners Cause if you're wanted Then
you're a winner For we are on the
cruise And freedom is the only rule
Fearless night and day
Cause that's just our way
Find one piece I'll be the first I'll
put it be so bad I'll be the first
It's all this real It must be cause my
hand's on the wheel I'm done playing,
filled with the waiting In a world
I'm feeling alive, but I'll be loud
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far
Gotta make it to the end
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward
Dreaming from the very first day,
I'd make my name And don't you
know that dream hasn't changed
I'm done playing through,
it's a wave in the air The world
I'm feeling alive, look out below
Wake up, sunshine
Wake up, sunshine, here we go
We go
It doesn't have any
bones And I am only bones
That's interesting, I wonder if
it enjoys making no skull jokes?
Yeah, I doubt it!
Hey, you're a pretty good artist.
I wanted to capture the moment on paper!
Drive pictures? Really?
I'll help you out.
You've got a plan, right?
Problem is, there's not
much we can do underwater.
No, no, no.
The problem is, the thing's gigantic.
We couldn't even take
it on above sea level.
What is wrong with these people?
Anybody in their right mind would
have run for the hills by now.
What's taking them so long
to decide? We're leaving.
Shift the helm due south.
Hey, Nami!
Let's go straight towards it!
Don't be stupid! That thing is...
It's okay, Nami.
I'm here for you.
Who are you?
You held it in!
Good job!
We made him all better.
Well, it helps that
Nami put on a coat, too.
I'm not safe on this ship.
I'll have to protect myself.
Something's coming up behind us.
Huh?
Brother!
These guys again?
Ah, I'm so happy you came back for me.
You're the best crew a
captain could ask for.
Let's rush in there and rescue my brother!
Stop it!
It destroyed the coating!
That ship's bigger than the Sonny!
Oh, they didn't make it.
Like jellyfish.
That's too cruel!
Here it goes!
It's so cute!
Now they're cute! No!
If you do that, you'll
break the bubble for sure!
Chicken voyage!
Can't we escape somehow?
Wait, let me take care of it. Don't go!
If you pop the bubble, then we all die!
The little fellow's right, but if you
want to face the crack of that badly,
I might just have the idea for you.
There! Perfect!
That contraption is called
the flutter kick coating.
It's an extravehicular diving suit.
If I let them call the shots, we'll
all go to hell in a handbasket.
Hey, you weren't supposed to do that!
The rest of us wanted to get out of here!
Now they're going to stay
and try to fight that thing!
I've been telling you all to
run away from the beginning.
But your fearless leader
was having none of that.
Now was he?
Think of it this way.
Would you rather have to fight it outside
or fight it right here on the ship?
Right!
You guys get out there!
Far, far away!
This rope's kind of annoying.
Remember to stay as far
from the ship as you can!
Huh?
Wait a sec!
You guys forgot the safety ropes!
You're gonna get separated!
Sounds like Nami's worried about me.
Listen up!
I need both of you guys to distract him.
If I can get one good punch
off, I think I can take him.
Why don't I just slice him to pieces?
It'd be easier.
Because that wouldn't do me any good!
I want to capture him
and keep him as a pet!
Okay, that was way too close!
Crazy!
Rocket Launcher!
Got him!
That was incredible!
Not another one!
He lost his account!
Guard point!
Whoa, he hit the ship pretty hard.
Everyone okay?
He saved us!
Thanks, buddy!
Nice one, Chopper!
You're about to be crushed
against that mountain!
Now, feel true!
Pigantesco Moon!
Wow, those hands are big!
Nice one, Robin!
That was close!
Thank goodness.
I was only in the water for the
briefest moment, so my power held out.
Now, third gear!
Armament Hartnick!
So tough! Underwater! Come on!
Oh crap it doesn't look like that octopus
is gonna wait patiently blue walk.
Oh my Sanji just left his
bubble he's fast even in
the sea like a fish man
so cool I spent two years
running from those monsters
on that island and the
first thing I do is run
straight at another one.
But all things considered,
this one's a bit cuter, really.
Diable Jomber!
And Queen!
We'll shoot!
Three-sword style.
Crossing the six paths!
Wow, yeah, I couldn't
even see his attack, hey?
He blew it away!
What kind of training
did Luffy go through?
What the?
Did I see that?
Yeah, why is that shark wearing a shirt?
Not to mention it's huge.
What's up?
The sea current is pulling us in.
You're being swept away
by the downward current.
You can't get split up down here.
Follow them. Right.
I don't want to die down here.
It's dark and wet.
What, you fools?
Pull it together.
That dude was there.
Panicking.
If I had a stomach, I would be
fighting against conscience right now.
Keep it your quibble, Franky.
Turn hard to port, otherwise
we're going to crash!
All right, I'm on it!
Don't let up for a second
or the ship's on her!
Let's keep it together, everybody!
Stay in the center of the current!
It's way too fast!
You're awake ah what a headache but at
least we made it what's
wrong why are you all
making such long faces i mean i'm awake
now so there's nothing for you to fear man
is it freezing luffy zoro and sanji have
gone missing they're lost in the sea what
the most we can do now is hope the monster
didn't tear them apart glad you're being
optimistic how are we supposed to find
them when we can't even see what's in front
of us i don't like being in the dark it
feels like something could attack us from
any direction the best i can guess is
we've descended about 7 000 meters even the
shark submerged can't
sustain this level of
pressure how close are
we to fishman island
maybe the others have already
made it there probably
not according to Kuma it's
10 000 meters below sea level
and we have three thousand
more to go those guys each
have a bubble and that's all
even if they are somehow still
alive they'll need more
air none of this would have
happened if they used the
safety ropes freaking out's not
helping so let's get to work
we can look for him with my
new searchlight does it shine
from your eyes you'll see?
Cranky nipple legs!
Why do they have to be there?!
No!
Let's get out of here!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Where in the world have you guys gone?
We need you all fast!
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
This place is so fast, and we're so far
down, Sunny's eyes are practically useless.
I feel so helpless.
We can barely see.
It's no wonder that everyone's on edge.
There's gotta be a better
way to tackle this.
You ladies got any ideas?
Keep searching and just hope for the best.
We can't stop the ship right now.
Look, a jellyfish!
It's like we're inside it!
It's huge!
It feels like it could swallow us whole!
And they're twinkling!
It's like a starry sky wherever they go!
Oh, they're so beautiful!
Whoa, that's one long tentacle!
You, uh, want to shake
hands and be friends?
Whatever you do, don't touch it!
It's probably venomous!
Oh, crap!
No choice!
Coup de Burst!
No way!
It ain't that big jellyfish hole!
Uh, not to mention we lost
some air in that maneuver.
It was better than the alternative.
But yeah, the coup de burst sucks
in air to make a quick launch.
Thing is, because we're underwater,
it's only resources our air supply.
So obviously, when we use
it, our bubble shrinks a bit.
The fish that attacked
it turned upside down!
A neurotoxin.
I figured as much.
It's awful down here!
And dark!
It's scary!
All these creepy creatures
with their freaky eyes!
Because the sea is so dark,
many of the animals that live
down here have poor eyesight.
However there were some that
have very developed eyes as well.
Oh you're curious as to how I can see when
I don't have eyes it's
a secret hey Brooke?
Why is it you're always
talking to yourself?
It's a habit that comes
from being lonely. Enough!
Quit fooling around!
No more violence, please!
Luffy! Zoro! City!
Help us!
Nami is scary!
What's this?
Well, that's not good.
Hey, guys?
Huh?
Have any of you seen the
pirate who boarded the ship?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot about him.
I'm sure he's around here somewhere.
But where is somewhere?
I haven't seen him for a while.
Not since we descended.
Do you think he might have been
thrown off when everything went crazy?
Totally possible.
I mean, his arms and legs were tied up.
There's no way he could hold on to
anything while we were rocking around.
Normally, I'd agree.
But it seems that he freed himself. Look.
so that Drop weirdo escaped and he's still
here he's got to be
waiting us out for a moment
to attack this is bad
if you're so eager to
see me i'd be happy to
sneak into your room
tonight sweetheart damn
it we've got enough
problems we don't need
this guy giving us one
more thing to worry
about don't get worked up
it's not like he's an
actual threat to any of us
That's right, you think that.
You'll see how wrong you are now
that the three morons who could
put up a fight have gotten themselves
killed fighting that kraken.
After all,
there's no way they survive
getting sucked down into the bowels
of the ocean with just those
tiny bubbles to protect them.
What a shame I didn't have the chance
to kill Straw Hat with my own hands.
But no one will ever doubt that
he's dead once I come back with
the rest of his crew members heads
in tow as my personal trophies.
No one at all.
But I can't get too excited.
There's no need to rush.
If I killed them all now, there wouldn't
be anyone left to sail the ship!
And then what would I do?
So I'll let them live for now while
they can still be useful to me.
Once we land on Fishman Island though, I'm
gonna slaughter you down to the last man!
Let's see a break out of that.
How did he even manage to
get in there because we
weren't paying attention to
him if he weren't so stupid?
We could have been in trouble.
His body was like a big
mass of goo in there.
It didn't have a real shape
So he was like a pile of mud.
Yeah, if I had to guess
the Devil Fruit power
Most likely a logia type fruit at
that he was giving us a false sense
of security because he could have
escaped at any time Get me out of here!
I'll behave, I swear!
You and the banana hammock, and if
you let me out, I'll be your servant!
Come on!
You feeling all right, Chopper?
I don't know.
It just got really hot.
I can't stand the heat.
I'm dying.
Chouchou!
It is warmer.
Wait a second. Is that smoke?
We can't see what's in
front of us through that!
Smoke under the water?
Can't be.
Actually, it can.
Is that...
Hydro-thermal deposits.
What?
Keep up.
This is a volcanic area. For real?
Yes, for real.
You can see where there
have been eruptions.
We have to get out of here now.
If one of those erupts,
we're just gonna stand.
It's hot.
I'm so hot.
There's something coming after us!
It's carnivorous tube worms!
You've got no choice. Small one.
Coup de burst!
Chase those crabs!
Have to risk it again. Coup de burst!
I don't even know what
the hell those things are!
Hang on, guys.
Coup de burst!
The sea is awful.
I hate it.
There's no way the others can
survive down here on their own.
I can't believe this is happening!
And we'd only just gotten back together.
Stop crying.
Those three are way too tough to die.
Even using coup to burst that sparingly,
we've lost so much air already.
What is that?
A light in the darkness.
Wait.
Is that Fishman Island?
Maybe Luffy beat us there.
It can't be.
We haven't descended
the last 3,000 meters.
Who are you?
A friend?
Stop!
If you want to flash signals,
do it without actually flashing!
Can you tell what it is?
No, it's still too bright to see.
Oh, no!
An anglerfish! We're screwed!
The deep-sea hunter fooled us.
Hook, line, and sink her!
A little close that time!
There isn't anywhere left for us to run.
What can we do?
This can't be happening!
It's human?
No, this isn't making a sea!
A sea monster?
That's taking the form of a man!
It's a sea monster!
He's going to capsize the ship!
What the?
Hey, that's naughty.
You know better, Ancaro.
You're not allowed to eat ships.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Captain Vandor Deccan won't be
happy when he hears about this.
Wait, did he just help us?
Who freaking cares?
Let's just make a break for it.
He might change his mind.
Dead men tell no tales,
and dead men have mercy.
I pluck the rings right off their
hands within these shadowy seas.
Dead men have no regrets
and no tears left to weep.
I'll pluck the crowns right off their
heads within this cold, black deep.
Sunken treasures free
for the taking A king
of pirates in the making
I leave my enemies
weeping and shaking Vander Decken is my
name And these long-lost riches I do claim
No way!
Now we can't be!
It's a ghost ship!
You are the last one who should be scared!
Nothing would make me happier,
but take a look at their sail!
That's the legendary Flying Dutchman!
It shouldn't be here!
It shouldn't exist!
As the story goes, it sailed
the seas hundreds of years ago.
One dark and stormy night, the captain
of the ship suddenly lost his mind.
Consumed with madness, he threw his own
crewmates into the sea one after another.
Then he turned his gaze to the
heavens and cursed the very gods.
The captain's name was none
other than Vander Decken,
and the ship was the Flying Dutchman.
The gods condemned him for his actions,
and he was cursed for all eternity.
Sailing the seas aimlessly.
Theron and Mary Vassal.
Even if you're a skeleton who has sailed.
On a ghost ship of your own.
The sight of the flying Dutchman.
Will put chills down your spine.
Listen up.
I'm not digging their
treasure out of your stomachs.
So no eating the ship.
Just give it a good knock.
You bitch.
I think we're about to get pounded.
Well sure, he's our enemy.
Franky, we need a coup de purse.
I can't.
We used up all our fuel already.
That means we're on our own till
I can restock the cola supply.
That's the monster of
the Arctic, the Kraken.
You big boy!
All right, he learned his lesson. Enough!
Good boy.
Hey!
Guys, I thought you were dead!
That was so scary!
What the heck happened to you?
Mommy Swan! Robin!
It was crazy, that's for sure!
They got lost. Morons.
They're hopeless without me.
Are you gonna take that, Watasumi?
Get back up!
Avenge yourself! Start swinging!
My bubble popped and so did Sanji,
so we all had to crowd inside
Zoro's before he drowned!
We're running out of air!
How about you stop scaring us like that?
Now a song for you, captain?
No
kidding,
and you tamed the kraken
just like you said.
I thought you were nuts.
So is he going to be our new guy?
Yeah!
If that Cape dude can have
a sea monster pull his ship,
then we can have Tsurume pull the Sunny!
Right, pal?
Of course you would name
it already, wouldn't you?
That's cool if he wants
to give us a free ride.
But make sure he doesn't crush
us with those giant tentacles.
What's that?
Captain, stop!
We gotta turn back or we're dead!
I knew it.
An undersea volcano.
Straight ahead!